Hell on the Border is a western, adventure film directed by Wes Miller.
In the late 1800s, legendary marshal Bass Reeves sets out on
the trail of notorious outlaw Bob Dozier.
Charlie Storm, played by Ron Perlman.
Bob Dozier, played by Frank Grillo.
Bass Reeves, played by David Gyasi.
Irish Jack, played by Randy Wayne.
Issac Parker, played by Manu Intiraymi.
Tom Pinkerton, played by Gianni Capaldi.
Hell on the Border is a 2019 American Western film written and directed by Wes
Miller and starring David Gyasi, Ron Perlman and Frank Grillo.
It includes characters based on the true story of Bass
Reeves, the first African-American deputy U.S.
Marshal west of the Mississippi River.